PROPHECY TIME
A child is crying, a baby.
Yes.
He is crying, “Where is my father?”
There is a controversy over a child.
PROPHECY CONFIRMATION
My name is Ikenna Nnebor.
I am from Anambra State but I reside in Cameroon.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was business failure.
One night when I slept, I dreamt and saw Prophet T.B. Joshua and a small boy sitting on seats.
Prophet T.B. Joshua told me to come.
There was water there so he asked me to go through it and come to him.
I said no because I would fall inside the water.
He told me to come.
I wanted to hold onto something but fell, yet the water was not deep.
When I reached T.B. Joshua, he started telling me many things.
After that, he gave me bread to eat. So, I ate it.
I then told my wife I wanted to go to The SCOAN in Nigeria.
I borrowed money and I came to The SCOAN.
When I reached The SCOAN, I sat at the back.
The man of God came to me and said that there was a child crying and asking about his father.
When the man of God gave me the prophecy, I was surprised.
I didn’t understand the prophecy.
I went to my hotel room and slept.
After the man of God gave me the prophecy, I saw everything in a dream.
I saw the lady and remembered that it was eight years ago.
I met with that girl in Ogbunike.
I remember everything.
I came back to The SCOAN and explained to them.
They told me to go and find the child.
I sent my friend and sister to go and look for the boy.
When they asked her family, they said that the girl had already married but the grandmother was with the child.
I told them to ask the grandmother whose child it was.
The family said that they didn’t know his father.
The daughter told them that nobody cared about the boy.
The man of God told me to go and find the boy.
When I visited the family, I saw a little boy playing outside.
Something told me that this was the child.
One of my friends followed me there.
Something told me that this was my child.
I asked a woman there, who the child was.
They said that this was the child they talked about.
This was the child the man of God told me about.
From there, we discussed how to come to The SCOAN.
They said, they would follow me to The SCOAN to confirm the prophecy of the man of God.
It was an evangelist that called him to come, to stand and to think about what the man of God said.
He said, "No, there is nothing like that".
"There in nothing like that."
The evangelist calls him and says, "Take it easy. Go and think about it".
That is how this man walked out and went back to the hotel.
When he arrived at the hotel, he thought, "I came here with a problem and they tell me about a child.
A child is crying. What kind of a problem is this? This is another problem. I said that my business was down
and they added another problem to me."
That is what he was thinking; "My business collapsed, I have nowhere to live.
Instead of this man solving my problem, he gives me another problem".
His heart was so disturbed.
In the hotel he stared to think about what was said.
He was only thinking about what to eat and where to sleep.
While he was sleeping he saw in the vision the woman he met long time ago.
The Lord showed him, "This is the woman we are talking about. Are you saying you don't know this woman?"
"I Slept With Her ONLY ONCE..." | TB Joshua PROPHECY!...
"Are you saying you don't know this woman?!"
He woke up and started thinking, "Yes! It is true. The woman said she was pregnant. That day."
He started calling friends, everyone, they say - the woman had given a birth to a baby boy.
The boy is in the village.
He has no father.
That is how he came back and said, "I am very sorry. I remember now. Help me."
We said, "OK, in Jesus' name."
He was afraid to that place.
We said, "Go, nothing will happen to you."
On getting there, he entered the village; nobody knew him, until he looked for the women he slept with.
The woman had married with somebody and has other babies.
The woman came and said, "Yes, I know this man. He slept with me. He is the one."
"I Slept With Her ONLY ONCE..." | TB Joshua PROPHECY!
Tell me - this is beyond human what?
[Comprehension.]
I didn’t know the girl.
I just met the girl once at my friend’s house and made love with that girl only once.
"I Slept With Her ONLY ONCE..." | TB Joshua PROPHECY!
Look, my brother, when you look at your life, from the beginning to the present, you will know that
those things that give you headache and problems, they are "only once".
Only once.
But "only once" is already an abuse - you enter the trouble.
Just, "I will give it to you - only once".
Many are in the graveyard because of "only once".
Anytime a thief is caught and you move close to the thief and ask him, "Are you a robber?"
"Yes. Only once."
Those who had been robbing for many years - they never catch them.
"Only once."
If they are being shot, and they did not die, and you ask the person in the pool of blood, "What led you to rob?"
"It was only once."
I met the girl only once.
Then, I travelled to Cameroon.
Two months later, my brother called me on the phone.
He said that girl was pregnant.
I said, “Whether she’s pregnant is not my business. What is my concern?”
Can you see?
Now, he is confessing that he knew there was something like that.
Therefore, we are here together with the little boy, his mother and the younger brother of that girl.
That is this little boy.
Can you see his face and that man's face?
Mr. "only once".
That is the man and the little boy.
You can see the resemblance.
Mr. "only once".
Look at these two faces.
Now, what next?
Whatever this man lays hand on..., he should go to the village and pay all the money they have spent
on this small child.
He should give them some huge money to thank them.
Now, take this child to go to school, and bring the child to himself and whatever he lay hand...
The road that was closed will open.
"I Slept With Her ONLY ONCE..." | TB Joshua PROPHECY!
Go to the village, pay the money.
All the care and love they have given to this boy...
Go and see the elders, not only the mother and say you are sorry.
You cannot pay them once.
You need to continue to go there and thank them.
It is not something you can just go...
Even trillion dollar cannot pay that care and love.
You have to go there every time - no matter how much you give them,
you need to be going there to see how they are doing.
Carry this child, put him in a good school, let him be with you, be a father.
God wants to revise all the curses on you, the road that is blocked will be open.
My name is Esther Ezegbo.
I didn’t know this man before.
When your daughter, the mother of the child, saw him, what did she say?
My daughter said that this man had this child.
Let's hear the little boy.
How are you?
I'm fine.
Thank you momma.
I will sit with you people, we will discuss - so thank you very much.
Thank you.
Momma - I will see you.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today,
and stay up to date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, sermons, and testimonies from SCOAN
Emmanuel TV; changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.